Everything's on hold till I make the announcement.
在我正式宣布之前一切都暂停，
That's not for a few weeks.
还有几个星期.
-Then all hell breaks loose. -Yep
-接下来所有的事情都会乱哄哄的. -Yep
Joe, you've been doing this for two days.
Joe,这两天你一直在这样，
Is your neck bothering you?
你是不是脖子疼?
Maybe you should see a doctor.
也许你该去看看医生.
You're right. If it doesn't get better soon.
你说得没错. 如果还不快点好的话，
I'll have to have it looked at.
我就得请人看看了.
It's probably from the train.
可能是坐火车引起的.
What happened on the train?
火车上怎么啦?
We went to New York.
我们上次到纽约去，
On the way back, the train was delayed.
结果在回来的路上，火车给延误了.
For how long?
延误了多长时间?
Five hours. We stopped somewhere in Connecticut for five hours.
5个小时.火车在Connecticut的一个地方停了5个小时.
No wonder your neck's bothering you.
难怪你的脖子会疼.
My back would be a mess.
要是我的话，连背也会受不了的.
I told Marie we should have flown.
我跟Marie说我们应该飞回来的.
We should have taken the shuttle.
我们本来就该乘往返巴士的，
But she wouldn't listen.
可她就是不听.
Now I have a pain in the neck.
现在弄得我脖子疼.
Well, you have to admit, the delay wasn't Marie's fault.
Well,不过你得承认，火车延误可不能怪Marie.
Yeah, yeah. I probably shouldn't.
Yeah, yeah. 也许我不应该.
You and Marie are traveling a lot lately.
你和Marie最近经常出去旅游吗?
We're putting the romance back in our marriage.
我们打算把浪漫的感觉重新带回到我们的婚姻生活中来.
I'll let you know if it works.
如果这样做真有效果的话, 我会告诉你的.
What did you order?
你点的是什么?
Turkey club.
火鸡三明治.
What did you get?
你拿到的是什么?
Peanut butter and jelly. Bon appetite.
花生酱果冻三明治. 祝你胃口好.